THE NEW GATE.
A totally unprecedented next-generation
VR MMORPG that uses bleeding-edge technology.
Adventure freely throughout
the world you see before you.
Elf
Beast
Choose from seven unique species
to create your avatar.
Dragnir
Dwarf
Pixie
Lord
Human
Defeat powerful monsters with allies,
earn a fortune through trade,
or become a blacksmith
and forge legendary weapons.
The VR MMORPG that allows you to do
everything you can imagine, THE NEW GATE.
Currently available in all regions.
One day, "THE NEW GATE"
became a death game.
It became impossible to log out,
and deaths within the game
became deaths in real life.
Are you...
Are you the Shin?
In order to end that hopeless game,
I kept on fighting.
Master, you're leaving already?
If we ever meet again,
I hope we can have a proper duel.
Take care.
Sure. I'll be back.
Like a true final boss,
it's quick despite its size.
But your head is mine!
Damn. It dodged it.
Stay calm. Once I defeat it,
then all of this...
Gatekeeper
Origin
Its damaged parts are healing?
Not on my watch!
Steel Strike!
Gatekeeper
Origin
It's healing again, but...
Moonlight Blade Dance!
This ends now!
Gatekeeper Origin has been defeated.
Acquired titles "the Critical,"
"the Achiever," and "the Liberator."
The dungeon has been cleared.
Players can now log out.
It's finally over.
I'd better check if everyone
managed to log out.
They're disappearing.
Everyone's leaving the game world successfully.
Shin
I'm the last one.
Sistem
Player Guide
Settings
Log Out
Goodbye, THE NEW GATE.
What's going on?
There shouldn't be any more events.
I thought I had beaten the game.
Is this the game world?
No, it's too realistic.
I know VR technology
has made massive strides,
but it shouldn't be this realistic.
Oh, I know.
So I can pull up windows.
Wait, my stats have improved significantly!
Is it because of the titles I acquired
by beating the final boss?
Well, if I beat the game,
I should be able to log out.
It's not here.
Elimină
Creează
Colectează
Ghidul jucătorului
Setări
There's no log out button?
You can't be serious. Oh, I know.
What about the others?
You are not connected to the network.
Page cannot be displayed.
I can't connect to the network?
Then the game shouldn't allow me to move.
Does that mean this is reality?
I don't get it.
First a death game, now an isekai trip?
I'll never get anywhere sticking around here.
If I can use this item set to my home base...
All right. Back to my house.
When was this wall built?
I saw a castle, too. Is this all one town?
There it is.
Home sweet home.
Don't make me say it again.
My master won't be back for a while.
You're just hiding her, aren't you?
If you refuse to tell us,
we'll have to use force.
Stop. If I go any farther outside...
I see.
I can adjust the power of my magic skills.
Physical attacks impose some strain on me.
It feels so real.
Um, excuse me...
Uh, I'm ho...me?
Moon Sanctum
Thank you for saving me. I am Tiera Lucent.
I'm Shin.
Shin, is it?
Shin, do you know my master?
You just said, "I'm home."
Your master?
What are you saying?
There isn't anyone who doesn't know acting
shopkeeper of the Moon Sanctum, Schnee Raizar.
Schnee Raizar, huh? Schnee...
Schnee Raizar?!
Is she a beautiful high elf with waist-length
silver hair and an incredible body?
If she's not someone else
with the exact same name,
Schnee is one of my support characters.
I mean, the Moon Sanctum exists, so...
Oh, uh, you could say Schnee and I go way back.
So, where is she now?
I can't easily share that information.
We only just met, and those guys
were looking for her, too.
But I can at least take a message.
A message?
My job is to look after the store
and take messages for my master.
Each message will cost you 1,000 jules.
A thousand jules? But I only have jales.
Wait a minute. Did you just
take that out of an item box?
Yeah. What about it?
What about it?
Only kings and elders of a limited number
of species can use those.
Not only that, but gold jale coins
are an item for amplifying magic.
They're worth at least ten billion jules.
Ten billion?
In the game, jales were
the smallest form of currency.
Seriously, who are you?
Just an ordinary adventurer.
Setting-wise... well, my species is high human.
High human?
But the high humans went extinct.
Extinct? You mean humanity is extinct?
Only the high-ranking ones,
the high humans, went extinct.
You just saw some humans earlier.
Oh, right.
There were once only six high humans.
They went missing during
the Dusk of Prosperity 500 years ago.
The Dusk of Prosperity?
You don't even know what that is?
It was a major historical event when not only
high humans but many people vanished.
A bunch of people vanished? Could it be?
Tens of thousands of players
were trapped in the game then.
Ako
Tera
It certainly would be a major event
if that many people went missing at once.
Shin
So the simplest interpretation is...
This world is 500 years
after the events of the game?
Hey, are you listening?
Oh, uh, thanks for telling me.
You can have this.
What?
I look forward to getting to know you.
Did you hear what I said earlier?
What kind of idiot just gives something
so valuable to someone?
This kind.
You won't ask for it back?
Nope.
I've dreamed of holding a gold jale coin.
They're so shiny and have a beautiful design.
W-Well, since elves use magic,
it should be useful to you.
Elves?
Do I look like an elf to you?
Yeah, you're very obviously a black-haired,
golden-eyed, beautiful elf girl.
I don't believe it.
I even had my master
cast an illusion spell on me.
Why would you do that?
Because black-haired elves
are a cursed symbol of misfortune.
A symbol of misfortune?
Yes. This black hair brings misfortune.
Monsters began attacking frequently,
and I was kicked out of my village.
My master rescued me then.
There's a barrier around this shop,
and my master uses
an illusion spell to hide my identity.
I've lived in safety for 100 years.
I see. They were attacked earlier
because of that curse.
Is there any way to remove the curse?
Not that we know of,
though my master is looking into it.
But it's fine.
Even if I can't leave the barrier,
as long as I can live without bothering anyone.
Still...
Has your hair always been black?
No. It used to be silver.
But one day, I was suddenly cursed,
and it turned black.
Suddenly?
A curse that suddenly changes one's hair color.
Monster attacks. Is that even...
It is. It is possible!
Huh?
I can't believe I forgot.
Let's see. Open skill screen, and...
It should be around here.
Um, what are you doing?
Found it. Analyze.
I knew it.
Cadou Blestemat
Analyze X
Huh? What do you mean?
You have the cursed title Cursed Gift.
Analyze X
Cursed Gift
It's the reason your hair changed color
and monsters started attacking you.
It's a randomly occurring curse.
But just identifying the curse won't fix it.
There is a way to remove your curse.
What?
Here we go.
Purify.
Huh?
It didn't work?
No, the Purify worked.
But only a bit of your hair changed back.
Tiera. I don't know how to put this...
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
But...
It's fine. This is great. Better than great.
I got back my hair
that I haven't seen in 100 years.
I'm sorry I lost my composure.
But it's hard to believe
the curse has really been lifted.
Then why don't you try exiting the barrier?
What?
You'll be okay.
If any monsters show up, I'll defeat them.
Moon Sanctum
I don't know about this...
You've been patiently waiting
for 100 years, right?
You'll be okay.
Okay, let's go.
Nothing's happening.
You're right.
The curse has been lifted.
Seems like it.
Hey, Shin.
The sky is huge, isn't it?
Yeah.
Moon Sanctum
I'm glad I could be useful.
Thank you so much.
What are you going to do now, Shin?
My master won't be back for a while.
Then maybe I'll check out the nearby town.
I need to learn more about this world.
If her master is the real Schnee,
it's likely my other
support characters exist, too.
I know.
If you're going to Bayrelicht Kingdom,
you should take this with you.
Bay...?
I guess that's the place I passed by earlier.
Here. It's a letter of introduction.
When you enter the kingdom,
there's a line to get inspected,
but this will allow you to bypass it.
Thanks, but are you sure you want to give
this letter to someone you just met today?
You lifted my curse, and you seem capable.
Besides, you're stupidly good-natured.
You didn't have to say that last bit.
I can't thank you enough.
What was that?
Nothing. It was nothing!
Well, I should get going.
I'll let you know once my master's back.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
I can't believe I got to skip that line.
This letter of introduction sure is something.
Not only that, but in this kingdom,
they're like identification papers that
can get you an audience with the king.
You'd better not lose that.
S-Seriously?
This is the adventurers guild.
Well, see you around.
Thanks for the escort.
If I want to gather information,
I should start here.
Welcome to the adventurers guild.
How can I help you today?
Oh, uh... I'd like to register as an adventurer.
Applications are accepted
at the counter up the stairs to your left.
Got it.
Welcome. Would you like
to register as an adventurer?
What? Uh, yes, please.
Is something the matter?
You look just like the woman
on the first floor.
That's my older twin sister Celica.
I am Cilica.
Oh, I see.
First, we'll collect your initial fee,
and then you'll fill out this form.
I can't believe it takes a whole day
to create a guild card.
Copper and iron weapons.
All their armor is made of leather or iron.
Their equipment is lower quality
than it was in the game.
Thank you for waiting, Shin.
Celica? Why?
I help out here when I'm not busy.
Did you really need to change clothes, though?
Uh...?
Please, have some.
Okay.
It's good.
Stare...
But I can't eat like this.
Uh, Celica?
I'm sorry. There's actually something
I'd like to confirm with you.
I see. What is that?
I heard you have a letter of introduction
from the Moon Sanctum.
Yeah.
May I verify its authenticity in another room?
After I'm done eating, sure.
I don't really want to meet the guild
master right after showing up here.
About that...
He's actually already here.
Hey.
The weird guy at reception!
Nice to meet you.
I am Barlux Heim, the guild master.
I'm Shin. Nice to meet you.
Shin, let's cut to the case.
May I see your Moon Sanctum
letter of introduction?
Sure.
Let's verify its authenticity.
Huh?
When letters of introduction are placed
near each other, they resonate and glow.
I can attest this is an authentic letter.
I had no idea.
Who gave this to you?
What is Schnee? Tiera?
It was Tiera.
Something major must've happened
if she forgot to explain that to you.
Allow me to explain instead.
A letter of introduction allows you to enter
most nations without an inspection.
It's accepted by all guilds,
and in some nations, like Bayrelicht,
it even grants you an audience with the king.
They're the most trusted
form of identification.
Those are some insane benefits.
Schnee's really made a name for herself.
It's an extremely powerful item to have.
There are those who try to steal them
for nefarious purposes.
I'm sure there are.
So allow me to be direct.
If you're not confident you can protect
that letter, you should destroy it here.
I'll be fine.
If Tiera gave that to me because she
trusted me, then I won't let her down.
That's what I wanted to hear.
As one man recognized by the Moon Sanctum
to another, let's do our best to get along.
I look forward to seeing what you'll achieve.
Thank you.
Now, let's test your skills.
What?
Boy, I'm exhausted.
Today was a rough day.
I'll try raising my rank tomorrow,
once I get my guild card.
When is Schnee coming back?
Unfortunately, it looks like I didn't
wake up in the real world.
Good morning, Shin.
Did you sleep well?
Yes. Thanks to you,
I found a good inn to stay at.
Oh, you're wearing new clothes.
These are easier to move in.
A bottom-ranked adventurer
shouldn't dress so magnificently.
Here's your guild card.
[Shin]
Rang de aventurier
Card de breaslă
There are nine adventurer ranks,
from SS and S to A through G.
Completing jobs earns points,
allowing you to rank up.
You can take jobs up to
two ranks higher than your own.
I've already got a job I'd like to do.
Harvesting hilk grass, I see.
There's always demand for it as a potion
ingredient, so there's no time limit.
Got it.
Well, I'm off.
Be careful.
Barlux recognizes his skill,
but he isn't the slightest bit imposing.
What a strange person.
I've been looking for three hours now.
Even in the game, harvesting
hilk grass was a beginner quest.
I thought it would be easy.
Well, all the monsters are weak enough
to be beaten with low-ranking equipment,
so I'll take my time.
A monster. But why is it moving like that?
It should be nearby.
That's a Skullface Jack.
Monstru
Skullface Jack
Level 359. That's strong.
A wagon.
It must've looked odd on my map
because it was on a rampage.
Apparently someone attacked
by a Skullface Jack and killed.
I knew them. It's a real shame.
I have to do something about this.
I'll start by attacking.
It's quick.
And I've never heard of an undead monster
wielding a light-type sword before.
It must be a unique monster.
That wasn't much damage.
It can only handle one more blow.
Okay, let's try something.
Limit Off.
Look at it go.
I kind of wanted that sword, too.
It dropped a gemstone. I guess I'll take it.
I've more or less figured out
how strong I am in this world.
So the game is real here.
This is starting to get fun.
What happened?
Your Highness!
Is His Majesty all right?
Lady Rionne!
C-Ce s-a întâmplat aici?
Data viitoare
Episodul 2
Un partener mic